

Ravena Auliya Informatics Engineering Student

0895709085454 ravenaauliya@gmail.com Kepulauan Riau, Batam City

SUMMARY

Hi all...

My name is Ravena Auliya, my friends often call me Ravena. I am a student of Informatics Engineering, at Batam State Polytechnic. I started basic web programming in college. I think new knowledge is very interesting to explore. Also, at this time I am learning to focus on pursuing experiences that will definitely help me in the future. I can't just wait, I focus on trying. Apart from that, I also joined student organizations to train my soft skills. Both in public speaking and problem-solving.

EXPERIENCE

03/2023 - Present

UI/UX Designer & Coder Front End

Micro, Macro, & Massive Project Study Independent Batch 4

- In the micro project, we created UI/UX website for music concerts where audiences get information and buy concert tickets without queuing and jostling and of course with security lines.
- In the macro project, we created a macro project MPASI website which contains complementary information and recipes as well as a discussion forum. The output of this project is research, pipeline, and prototype to the front end.
- In the Massive Project, we create a Meddy website is a combined web and mobile
 development project with the idea of creating a drug app/web with lots of interesting features.
 For example tracking and selecting drugs as well as selecting the nearest pharmacy and online
 consultation. On the website itself, add a web admin as a CRUD record.

09/2022 - 12/2022

Front end & Back end

Brail Polibatam Robot Website (PBL)

Robot Brail Polibatam's website is a company profile website. This project is Project-based learning (PBL). I made the front end & back end main page using CI 4 Framework, PHP 8, Bootstrap

05/2022 - 08/2022

Back end

Tracer Study Alumni (Mini Pbl)

The Tracer Study Alumni website is a CRUD & MySQL based alumni data collection and tracking program.

EDUCATION

2023

WEB DEVELOPMENT

Infinite Learning

Study Independent Batch 4

Publication committee team in the Infinite Learning 2023 development festival.

INFORMATIC ENGINEERING

Batam State Polytechnic

D3 - Informatic Engineering

- Active member of informatics engineering association (HMTI), Education Sector.
- · LO KMIPN 2022 committee, PIC in the field of internet of things.

CERTIFICATES

02/2023 - Present Study Independent Batch 4 Infinite Learning

02/2022 - Present Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Informatika (HMTI)

SKILLS

HTML Intermediate CI 4 Beginner
CSS Intermediate PHP Beginner
UI/UX Design Intermediate React Js Beginner

JavaScript Beginner

LANGUAGES

Indonesia Native English Intermediate